export const questions = [{
    "question": "Genghis Khan's orginal name was...",
    "correct_answer": "Temujin",
    "questionOption":
        [
            "Ginesh",
            "Carl Drogo",
            "Genghis",
            "Temujin"
        ]},
    {
        "question": "When was Genghis Khan born?",
        "correct_answer": "1162",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "3000",
                "1164",
                "1464",
                "1162"
            ]},

    {"question": "You could describe Genghis Khan's military tactics as ...?",
        "correct_answer": "Aggressive",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "Relaxed",
                "Passive",
                "Aggressive",
                "He didn't fight ever!"
            ]},

    {"question": "What did Genghis Khan normally do to villages he came across?",
        "correct_answer": "Murder them",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "Murder them",
                "Shower them with gifts",
                "Introduce them to fine art and love",
                "Just ignore them"
            ]},
    {"question": "How many people is Genghis Khan believed to have helped to murder?",
        "correct_answer": "40 million",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "None! He was a good boy",
                "5 thousand",
                "30 million",
                "40 million"
            ]},
    {"question": "What percentage of the world's population is Genghis Khan's leadership estimated to have killed?",
        "correct_answer": "10%",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "5.0%",
                "3.7%",
                "0.2%",
                "10.0%"
            ]},
    {"question": "Where in the modern world was Genghis Khan born?",
        "correct_answer": "Mongolia",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "France",
                "Mongolia",
                "Finland",
                "China"
            ]},
    {"question": "What was Genghis Khan said to be holding in his hand when born?",
        "correct_answer": "Blood clot",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "Blood clot",
                "A star",
                "A mini figurine of Jesus christ",
                "The umbilical cord"
            ]},
    {"question": "What made the Mongols good at fighting?",
        "correct_answer": "Horsemanship and archery",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "Horsemanship and archery",
                "Overwhelming numbers",
                "Mad charges",
                "Semi-automatic weapons"
            ]},
    {"question": "How much land did Genghis Khan inherit when he became the head of his family",
        "correct_answer": "Nothing",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "10 million miles",
                "A small pasture",
                "Nothing",
                "5000 square miles"
            ]},
    {"question": "What does Genghis Khan's original name translate to",
        "correct_answer": "Iron worker",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "Fight king",
                "Iron fist",
                "Iron worker",
                "Flame worker"
            ]},
    {"question": "What was prophesied upon Genghis Khan's birth?",
        "correct_answer": "That he would be a great leader",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "That he would raise a dragon",
                "That he would be a great leader",
                "That he would turn out to be a fool",
                "That he would never be able to ride"
            ]},
    {"question": "What modern day city is Genghis Khan's birthplace closest to?",
        "correct_answer": "Ulaanbaatar",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "Ulaanbaatar",
                "Uladbanter",
                "New York",
                "Paris"
            ]},
    {"question": "How many official wives did Genghis Khan have?",
        "correct_answer": "4",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "1",
                "10",
                "2",
                "4"
            ]},
    {"question": "At its peak, how much land did Genghis Khan conquer?",
        "correct_answer": "Over ten million square miles",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "5 million square miles",
                "Over ten million square miles",
                "From shore to shore",
                "300 miles, and 300 more"
            ]},
    {"question": "How long did Genghis Khan's empire last after his death?",
        "correct_answer": "It fell quickly",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "Lasting 1000 years",
                "It still stands to this day!",
                "It fell quickly",
                "He is still alive!"
            ]},
    {"question": "In the Iranian plateau, how many people died due to Genghis Khan's influence?",
        "correct_answer": "Up to three quarters",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "Up to three quarters",
                "About half",
                "None",
                "All of them"
            ]},
    {"question": "What do people foolishly commend Genghis Khan for?",
        "correct_answer": "His religious tolerance",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "His religious tolerance",
                "His singing ability",
                "His strong and stable polices in regards to brexit",
                "His altitude towards slavery"
            ]},
    {"question": "How long did it take for the population of the Iranian plateau to recover from the massacre led by Genghis Khan?",
        "correct_answer": "until the 20th century",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "until the 18th century",
                "until the 19th century",
                "until the 20th century",
                "until the 21th century"
            ]},
    {"question": "What was the main reason for all the murdering Genghis Khan facilitated?",
        "correct_answer": "Expanding his empire!",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "For fun, he just loves killing!",
                "Expanding his empire!",
                "For cardiovascular exercise",
                "Because he had a banging hangover."
            ]},
    {"question": "Who split up Genghis Khan's empire after his death?",
        "correct_answer": "His grandchildren",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "His grandchildren",
                "His wife",
                "His mother",
                "His best friend Bob"
            ]},
    {"question": "What did Genghis Khan do to the nomadic tribes of Mongolia?",
        "correct_answer": "Unite them",
        "questionOption":
            [
                "Lead them west to discover America",
                "Exile them",
                "Kill them",
                "Unite them"
            ]},
];
